<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<p-contents>
    <p-section id="version-1.2.0" bottompadding="10" toppadding="5">
        <p-title level="3" underline="false">Version 1.2.0</p-title>
        <p-paragraph fontsize="13">
            Released on <i>April 24, 2026</i>.
        </p-paragraph>
        <p-list id="v1.2.0" style="number">
            <p-item>Refactored the runtime architecture by separating RetroArch rendering and game logic, with game logic now running on an independent thread for improved frame stability and responsiveness.</p-item>
            <p-item>Added fast-forward support with <b>2x / 3x / 4x / 6x</b> speed levels, reducing repetitive wait time and improving gameplay efficiency.</p-item>
            <p-item>Integrated <b>signalsmith-stretch</b> for audio smoothing during fast-forward, effectively reducing noise artifacts and improving overall listening quality.</p-item>
            <p-item>Upgraded configuration to a dual-layer model (core-level + game-level): set defaults per core and override them per game for finer-grained personalization.</p-item>
        </p-list>
    </p-section>
    <p-section id="version-1.1.0" bottompadding="10" toppadding="5">
        <p-title level="3" underline="false">Version 1.1.0</p-title>
        <p-paragraph fontsize="13">
            Released on <i>April 8, 2026</i>.
        </p-paragraph>
        <p-list id="v1.1.0" style="number">
            <p-item>Added a new <b>SpriteKit-based Overlay buttons</b> system to improve the in-game control and interaction experience.</p-item>
            <p-item>Added <b>smart multi-file ROM import detection</b> for both file import and folder import workflows.</p-item>
            <p-item>The importer can now automatically recognize grouped game files such as <b>cue, m3u, gdi, mds, and ccd</b>, detect missing referenced files, and handle grouped imports more reliably.</p-item>
            <p-item>Enhanced data security by migrating core files (Roms, Save States, Databases, etc.) to a <b>secure system directory</b>, preventing accidental deletion and ensuring a more stable app experience.</p-item>
        </p-list>
    </p-section>
    <p-section id="version-1.0" bottompadding="10" toppadding="5">
        <p-title level="3" underline="false">Version 1.0</p-title>
        <p-paragraph fontsize="13">
            Released on <i>March 22, 2026</i>.
        </p-paragraph>
        <p-list id="v1.0" style="bullet">
            <p-item>RetroGo was officially released on the App Store.</p-item>
        </p-list>
    </p-section>
</p-contents>
